A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1972-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 34553], 1990-1992, Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, Job Training Partnership Act, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health, Certificate of Public Need, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost Review Council, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Indians, Council on, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, General, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, General, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Virginia Treatment Center for Children, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Western State Hospital, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Rights of the Disabled, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Rights of the Disabled, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support, Constituent mail, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Volunteerism, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Women, Council on the Status of, General, 1990 (Box 3)
  - General files, A-Z, Misc., 1990 (Box 3)
  - Agency files, Aging, General, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Aging, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Children, General, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Children, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, General, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Deaf and Hard of Hearing, General, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, General, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, Job Training and Partnership Act, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health, General, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent mail, 1991 January-July (Box 4)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent mail, 1991 August-December (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Health, Health planning, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Health, Certificate of Public Need, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Health, Rural health, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, General, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost Review Council, General, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Indians, Council on, General, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, General, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, General, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, General, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Straight, Inc., 1991 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, PL 99-457, Part H, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, General, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, General, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Board of Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, General, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1991 January-May (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1991 June-September (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1991 October-December (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Local Consolidation Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Consolidation Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, General, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Abuse, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Foster Care, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Homes for Adults, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, General, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, Constituent mail, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Volunteerism, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Women, Council on the Status of, General, 1991 (Box 8)
  - General files, A-Z, Misc., 1991 (Box 8)
  - General files, Council on Community Services for Youth and Families, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Agency files, Aging, General, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Aging, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, General, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Child Day Care and Early Childhood Programs, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Deaf and Hard of Hearing, General, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, General, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Governor's Employment and Training, Job Training Partnership Act, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Health, General, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent mail, 1992 January-February (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent mail, 1992 March-June (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Health, Constituent mail, 1992 July-December (Box 9)
  - Agency files, Health, Certificate of Public Need, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, General, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Health Professions, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost Review Council, General, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Health Services Cost Review Council, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Indians, Council on, General, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, General, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, General, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Provider tax, General, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Provider Tax, Constituent mail, 1992 January-March (Box 10)
  - Agency files, Medical Assistance Services, Provider Tax, Constituent mail, 1992 March-May (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, General, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Constituent mail, 1992 January-February 15 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services, Constituent mail, 1992 February 16-December (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, General, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Rehabilitative Services, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, General, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Board for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, General, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Agency files, Social Services, General, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1992 January-March (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1992 April-July (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Constituent mail, 1992 August-December (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support Enforcement, General, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Child Support, Constituent mail, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Social Services, Home for Adults, 1992 (Box 12)
  - Agency files, Visually Handicapped, General, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Agency files, Volunteerism, General, 1992 (Box 13)
  - Agency files, Women, Council on the Status of, General, 1992 (Box 13)
  - General files, A-Z, Misc., 1992 (Box 13)
  - General files, Comprehensive Services Act, 1992 (Box 13)
  - General files, Health Care for All Virginians, 1992 (Box 13)
  - General files, Maternal and Child Health, 1992 (Box 13)
- Series VII: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 35147], 1993-1994, Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, Constituent mail, 1993 January-August (Box 1)
  - Casey Foundation, 1993 (Box 1)
  - P.L. 99-457, Part H, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, Regulations, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Rehabilitative Services, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Dept. for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, Constituent mail, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Board for Persons with Disabilities, Constituent mail, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Social Services, Constituent mail, 1993 October-December (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Social Services, Constituent mail, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Aging, Constituent mail, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Children, Deaf, GETD, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Child Support Enforcement, Constituent mail, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Social Services, Constituent mail, 1993 January-September (Box 3)
- Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 35869], 1994-1997, Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Correspondence, General, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, Agency head, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Office of the Governor, Chief of Staff (Jay Timmons), 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Office of the Governor, Policy Office, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Office of the Governor, Press Office (Ken Stroupe, Press Secretary), 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Legislators, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Support Services, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
  - Susan Allen, 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Secretary of Administration, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Commission on Local Government, Mandates on Local Government, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Dept. for the Aging, 1994, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Health, General correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Health, Abstinence education, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Health, Fatherhood Campaign, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Health, Pfiesteria laboratory, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Health, Safe drinking water, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Health Professions, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Health Services Cost Review Council (HSCRC), 1996 (Box 2)
  - Council on Indians, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, General correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, Medicaid for Aliens, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, General correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Northern Virginia Mental Health Institute, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Rehabilitative Services, 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Rights for Virginians with Disabilities, 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Social Services, General correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Social Services, Welfare Reform (Virginia Independence Program, Virginia Initiative for Employment not Welfare, and the Governor's Commission on Citizen Empowerment), 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Dept. for the Visually Handicapped, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
- Series IX: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 37779], 1970-1991, Extent: 46 cu. ft. (46 boxes). (Box 1-46)
  - State Health Commissioners, 1970-1977 (Box 1)
  - State Health Commissioners, 1970-1977 (Box 2)
  - State Health Commissioners, 1970-1977 (Box 3)
  - General, 1970-1979 (Box 4)
  - General, 1970-1979 (Box 5)
  - Subject files, 1970-1979 (Box 6)
  - Subject files, 1970-1979 (Box 7)
  - Budget, 1970-1979 (Box 8)
  - Budget, 1970-1979 (Box 9)
  - Other state agencies, 1972-1978 (Box 10)
  - Other state agencies, 1972-1978 (Box 11)
  - General, 1972-1978 (Box 12)
  - General, 1972-1978 (Box 13)
  - Other state agencies, 1973-1979 (Box 14)
  - Other state agencies, 1973-1979 (Box 15)
  - H.R. Priorities Commission # 3, 1974-1976 (Box 16)
  - H.R. Priorities Commission # 3, 1974-1976 (Box 17)
  - H.R. Priorities Commission # 4, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - H.R. Priorities Commission # 4, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - General, 1974-1978 (Box 20)
  - General, 1974-1978 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974-1978 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974-1978 (Box 23)
  - Commission on Human Resource Priorities and Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 24)
  - Memoranda, 1975-1977 (Box 25)
  - Subject files, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
  - Subject and chronological files, 1974-1976 (Box 27)
  - General Assembly, 1975-1978 (Box 28)
  - General Assembly, 1975-1978 (Box 29)
  - OSHR (Closed files), 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - OSHR (Closed files), 1975-1977 (Box 31)
  - State Planning and Community Affairs Commission, 1975-1978 (Box 32)
  - General Assembly, Correspondence, Cabinets, 1978 (Box 33)
  - General Assembly, Correspondence, Cabinets, 1978 (Box 34)
  - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1975-1983 (Box 35)
  - Dept. of Personnel and Training, 1972-1983 (Box 36)
  - Dept. of Health, Kepone study, ca. 1976 (Box 37)
  - General, 1978 (Box 38)
  - General, 1978 (Box 39)
  - Drug Abuse Control, 1978 (Box 40)
  - Drug Abuse Control, 1978 (Box 41)
  - News summaries, Cabinet meetings, 1978-1980 (Box 42)
  - News summaries, Cabinet meetings, 1978-1980 (Box 43)
  - Reports, 1978-1980 (Box 44)
  - Conferences, 1991 (Box 45)
  - Conferences, 1991 (Box 46)